Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-78. Wages
    - Colorado and Southern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 16)
    - Colorado and Southern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-79. Wages
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-1616, 1931-1952 (Box 558, Folder 18)
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 19)
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-81. Wages
    - Kansas City Southern Railroad. Kansas City, Shreveport and Gulf Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 21)
    - Kansas City Southern Railroad. Kansas City, Shreveport and Gulf Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 22)
    - Kansas City Southern Railroad. Kansas City, Shreveport and Gulf Terminal Company. Mediation Case No. A-3645, 1951-1953 (Box 558, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-82. Wages
    - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1944-1951 (Box 558, Folder 24)
    - Florida East Coast Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 558, Folder 25)
    - Florida East Coast Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 26)
    - Florida East Coast Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-84. Wages
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad. General, 1952 (Box 558, Folder 28)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad. General, 1948-1951 (Box 558, Folder 29)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 1)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 2)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5270. Adjustment in Rate of Pay of Recheck Clerks, 1956-1957 (Box 559, Folder 3)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5032, 1955-1957 (Box 559, Folder 4)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5031, 1955-1957 (Box 559, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-85. Wages
    - Ann Arbor Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 559, Folder 6)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 7)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-87. Wages
    - Fort Worth and Denver City Railway Company. General, 1937-1952 (Box 559, Folder 9)
    - Fort Worth and Denver City Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 10)
    - Fort Worth and Denver City Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-88. Wages
    - Indianapolis Union Railway, 1931-1951 (Box 559, Folder 12)
    - Indianapolis Union Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 13)
    - Indianapolis Union Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 408-90. Wages
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau. General, 1947-1955 (Box 559, Folder 15)
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau. Mediation Case No. A-3660, 1950-1954 (Box 559, Folder 16)
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 17)
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 559, Folder 18)
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau. Mediation Case No. A-4745, 1954-1955 (Box 559, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-91. Wages
    - Western Maryland Railroad, 1945-1955 (Box 559, Folder 20)
    - Western Maryland Railroad. 1957 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 21)
    - Western Maryland Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 22)
    - Western Maryland Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 559, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-93. Wages
    - Camas Prairie Railroad. General, 1932-1951 (Box 559, Folder 24)
    - Camas Prairie Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 559, Folder 25)
    - Camas Prairie Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 26)
    - Camas Prairie Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-95. Wages
    - Peoria and Pekin Union Railway, 1932-1951 (Box 559, Folder 28)
    - Peoria and Pekin Union Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 29)
    - Peoria and Pekin Union Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-96. Wages
    - Rutland Railroad. General, 1955 (Box 559, Folder 31)
    - Rutland Railroad. General, 1942-1954 (Box 559, Folder 32)
    - Rutland Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 33)
    - Rutland Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 559, Folder 34)
    - Rutland Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-4210, 1951-1955 (Box 559, Folder 35)
    - Rutland Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-1671. Reorganization, 1942-1951 (Box 559, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-97. Wages
    - Norfolk and Western Railway. General, 1941-1950 (Box 560, Folder 1)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway. Mediation Case No. A-4162, 1952-1953 (Box 560, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway. Mediation Case No. A-4014, 1952-1953 (Box 560, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-98. Wages
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois, 1932-1952 (Box 560, Folder 6)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 7)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-99. Wages
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1934-1951 (Box 560, Folder 9)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 10)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-100. Wages
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio Railroad. General, 1945-1950 (Box 560, Folder 12)
      1945-November 1950.
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 13)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 408-101. Wages
    - Atlanta Joint Terminals. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 560, Folder 15)
    - Atlanta Joint Terminals. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 16)
    - Atlanta Joint Terminals. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-102. Wages
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal Railroad of New Orleans, Louisiana. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 560, Folder 18)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal Railroad of New Orleans, Louisiana. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 19)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal Railroad of New Orleans, Louisiana. Mediation Case No. A-5026, 1955-1956 (Box 560, Folder 20)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal Railroad of New Orleans, Louisiana. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 408-103. Wages
    - Long Island Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 560, Folder 22)
    - Long Island Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 23)
    - Long Island Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-104. Wages
    - Central Railroad Company of New Jersey. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 25)
    - Central Railroad Company of New Jersey. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-106. Wages
    - Denver Union Terminal Railway, 1932-1954 (Box 560, Folder 27)
    - Denver Union Terminal Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-107. Wages
    - Houston Belt Terminal Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 29)
    - Houston Belt Terminal Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-108. Wages
    - Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 31)
    - Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 408-109. Wages
    - Kansas, Oklahoma and Gulf Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 560, Folder 33)
    - Kansas, Oklahoma and Gulf Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 34)
    - Kansas, Oklahoma and Gulf Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 35)
    - Kansas, Oklahoma and Gulf Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-4435, 1952-1954 (Box 560, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-110. Wages
    - Midland Valley Railroad. General, 1940-1951 (Box 560, Folder 37)
      June 1940-51.
    - Midland Valley Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 38)
    - Midland Valley Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 408-111. Wages
    - Maine Central Railroad and Portland Terminal, 1931-1952 (Box 560, Folder 40)
      1931-April 1952.
    - Maine Central Railroad and Portland Terminal. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 41)
    - Maine Central Railroad and Portland Terminal. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 560, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 408-112. Wages
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad ("Big Four Railroad"). New York Central Railroad. General, 1951-1957 (Box 560, Folder 43)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad ("Big Four Railroad"). New York Central Railroad. General, 1931-1950 (Box 561, Folder 1)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad ("Big Four Railroad"). New York Central Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5184, 1955-1960 (Box 561, Folder 2)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad ("Big Four Railroad"). New York Central Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 3)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad ("Big Four Railroad"). New York Central Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-113. Wages
    - New York, Chicago, and St. Louis Railroad Company ("Nickel Plate Road"). General, 1931-1951 (Box 561, Folder 5)
    - New York, Chicago, and St. Louis Railroad Company ("Nickel Plate Road"). 1955 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-114. Wages
    - Grand Trunk Eastern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-117. Wages
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis, Missouri. General, 1951-1953 (Box 561, Folder 8)
      April 1951-March 1953.
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis, Missouri. General, 1946-1951 (Box 561, Folder 9)
      1946-March 1951.
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis, Missouri. Red Caps, 1947-1953 (Box 561, Folder 10)
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis, Missouri. Agreements. Clerks, Red Caps. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 11)
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis, Missouri. Agreements. Clerks, Red Caps. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 12)
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis, Missouri. Mediation Case No. A-2877, 1947-1950 (Box 561, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-118. Wages
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad. General, 1950-1952 (Box 561, Folder 14)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad. New York Connecting Railroad. Union Freight Railroad, Boston, Massachusetts. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 15)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad. New York Connecting Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-119. Wages
    - Central Vermont Railway. General, 1931-1951 (Box 561, Folder 17)
    - Central Vermont Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 18)
    - Central Vermont Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-120. Wages
    - Gulf Coast Lines. General, 1947-1956 (Box 561, Folder 20)
    - Gulf Coast Lines. Missouri Pacific Railroad, Gulf Coast District. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 21)
    - Gulf Coast Lines. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 22)
    - Gulf Coast Lines. Mediation Case No. A-2495. Kingsville, Texas, 1946-1947 (Box 561, Folder 23)
    - Gulf Coast Lines. General, 1944-1946 (Box 561, Folder 24)
    - Gulf Coast Lines. Agreements, 1949 (Box 561, Folder 25)
      1949 March 19
    - Gulf Coast Lines. Wage Adjustments for Master Car Builders, 1932-1943 (Box 561, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-121. Wages
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1932-1938 (Box 561, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-122. Wages
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad. Potomac Yard. Richmond Terminal Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 28)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 561, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-123. Wages
    - Grand Trunk Lines. General, 1932-1945 (Box 561, Folder 30)
    - Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 1)
    - Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 408-124. Wages
    - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 562, Folder 3)
    - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 4)
    - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 5)
    - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad. Mediation Case No. C-2997. Automation of 40 Clerical Positions, Gibson, Indiana, 1960 (Box 562, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-125. Wages
    - Georgia Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 562, Folder 7)
    - Georgia Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 8)
    - Georgia Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 408-127. Wages
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad, 1932-1953 (Box 562, Folder 10)
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 562, Folder 11)
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 12)
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-2054, 1945-1946 (Box 562, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-128. Wages
    - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad. General, 1942-1949 (Box 562, Folder 14)
    - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 15)
    - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-130. Wages
    - Joplin Union Depot. General, 1938-1953 (Box 562, Folder 17)
    - Joplin Union Depot. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. (Box 562, Folder 18)
    - Joplin Union Depot. 1956 Wage Movement. (Box 562, Folder 19)
    - Joplin Union Depot. 1955 Wage Movement. (Box 562, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-132. Wages
    - Seaboard Air Line Railroad Company. General, 1945-1956 (Box 562, Folder 21)
    - Seaboard Air Line Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 22)
    - Seaboard Air Line Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-134. Wages
    - Chicago Junction Railway. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company. General, 1932-1951 (Box 562, Folder 24)
    - Chicago Junction Railway. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 562, Folder 25)
    - Chicago Junction Railway. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 26)
    - Chicago Junction Railway. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-135. Wages
    - New York, Ontario, and Western Railway. General, 1932-1956 (Box 562, Folder 28)
    - New York, Ontario, and Western Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 562, Folder 29)
    - New York, Ontario, and Western Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 30)
    - New York, Ontario, and Western Railway. Mediation Case No. A-3714, 1950-1951 (Box 562, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-136. Wages
    - Buffalo Stock Yards. New York Central Railroad Company. General, 1941-1954 (Box 562, Folder 32)
    - Buffalo Stock Yards. New York Central Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 33)
    - Buffalo Stock Yards. New York Central Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 408-137. Wages
    - Yakima Valley Transportation Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 562, Folder 35)
    - Yakima Valley Transportation Company. 1955 Wage Movement. 1956 Wage Movement, 1955-1957 (Box 562, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-138. Wages
    - Lambert Coal Pier, Barrett, F.R., Stevedore. General, 1954-1955 (Box 562, Folder 37)
    - Lambert Coal Pier, Barrett, F.R., Stevedore. General, 1942-1953 (Box 562, Folder 38)
    - Lambert's Point Coal Piers, Maher, W.C., Contractor. 1955 Wage Movement. 1956 Wage Movement, 1955-1957 (Box 562, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 408-139. Wages
    - Nashville Terminals. General, 1932-1958 (Box 562, Folder 40)
    - Nashville Terminals. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 41)
    - Nashville Terminals. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 562, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 408-140. Wages
    - Virginian Railway, 1941-1957 (Box 562, Folder 43)
    - Virginian Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 1)
    - Virginian Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 408-142. Wages
    - Birmingham Terminal Company. General, 1932-1952 (Box 563, Folder 3)
    - Birmingham Terminal Company. Chattanooga Station Company; Columbia Union Station Company; Durham Union Station Company; Meridian Terminal Company; Winston-Salem Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 4)
    - Birmingham Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-143. Wages
    - El Paso Union Passenger Depot Company. General, 1937-1950 (Box 563, Folder 6)
    - El Paso Union Passenger Depot Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 7)
    - El Paso Union Passenger Depot Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-144. Wages
    - Memphis Union Station Company. General, 1932-1954 (Box 563, Folder 9)
    - Memphis Union Station Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1964 (Box 563, Folder 10)
    - Memphis Union Station Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 11)
    - Memphis Union Station Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-146. Wages
    - Galveston, Houston, and Henderson Railroad Company. General, 1950-1957 (Box 563, Folder 13)
    - Galveston, Houston, and Henderson Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 14)
    - Galveston, Houston, and Henderson Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-147. Wages
    - Staten Island Rapid Transit. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 16)
    - Staten Island Rapid Transit. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-148. Wages
    - Dayton Union Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 18)
    - Dayton Union Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 19)
    - Dayton Union Railway. General, 1952-1954 (Box 563, Folder 20)
    - Dayton Union Depot. General. Mediation Case No. A-2478, 1932-1951 (Box 563, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 408-151. Wages
    - Atchison Union Depot and Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 563, Folder 22)
    - Atchison Union Depot and Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 23)
    - Atchison Union Depot and Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 24)
    - Atchison Union Depot and Railroad Company. General, 1945-1954 (Box 563, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 408-154. Wages
    - Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railroad, 1947-1953 (Box 563, Folder 26)
      1947-May 1953.
    - Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railroad. Clerical Employees, Ore Dock Employees, Coal Dock Employees. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 27)
    - Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railroad. Ore Dock and Coal Dock Employees. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-157. Wages
    - Wabash Railroad. General, 1945-1956 (Box 563, Folder 29)
    - Wabash Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 563, Folder 30)
    - Wabash Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 31)
    - Wabash Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 563, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 408-162. Wages
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad. General, 1937-1951 (Box 563, Folder 33)
    - There is no Box No. 564. (Box 564)
  - Sub-Series 408-162. Wages
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 1)
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 408-165. Wages
    - Green Bay and Western Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1964 (Box 565, Folder 3)
    - Green Bay and Western Railroad. Kewaunee, Green Bay and Western. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 4)
    - Green Bay and Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-166. Wages
    - Cincinnati, New Orleans, and Texas Pacific Railway Company. General, 1931-1938 (Box 565, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-169. Wages
    - Danville and Western Railway. General, 1941-1959 (Box 565, Folder 7)
    - Danville and Western Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-170. Wages
    - Weatherford, Mineral Wells, and Northwestern Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 565, Folder 9)
    - Weatherford, Mineral Wells, and Northwestern Railroad. General, 1941-1942 (Box 565, Folder 10)
    - Weatherford, Mineral Wells, and Northwestern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-171. Wages
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway. General, 1948-1956 (Box 565, Folder 12)
      1948-June 1956.
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 565, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway. Mediation Case No. A-3990, 1952 (Box 565, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-177. Wages
    - Grand Central Terminal, New York. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 565, Folder 17)
    - Grand Central Terminal, New York. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 18)
    - Grand Central Terminal, New York. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-178. Wages
    - Canadian Pacific Railway. General, 1944-1954 (Box 565, Folder 20)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway. United States Lines. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 21)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 408-180. Wages
    - Columbus and Greenville Railroad. General, 1948-1955 (Box 565, Folder 23)
      1948-January 17, 1955.
    - Columbus and Greenville Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 565, Folder 24)
    - Columbus and Greenville Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 25)
    - Columbus and Greenville Railroad. 40-Hour Week, 1950-1951 (Box 565, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-181. Wages
    - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad. Agreements. Clerical Employees; Ore Dock Employees. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 565, Folder 27)
    - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-182. Wages
    - Bush Terminal Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 565, Folder 29)
    - Bush Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 30)
    - Bush Terminal Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-183. Wages
    - Canadian National Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 408-186. Wages
    - Joliet Union Depot. General, 1938-1958 (Box 565, Folder 33)
    - Joliet Union Depot. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 565, Folder 34)
    - Joliet Union Depot. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 35)
    - Joliet Union Depot. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 565, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-187. Wages
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company. General, 1953-1955 (Box 565, Folder 37)
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company., 1931-1952 (Box 565, Folder 38)
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 39)
    - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 565, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 408-188. Wages
    - Chicago Union Station Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 565, Folder 41)